<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Evans Tucker</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Evans Tucker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>[CC0](http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/) Evans Tucker has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 10:28:22 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tech Monopolies</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-06-17-tech-monopolies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 10:28:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-06-17-tech-monopolies/</guid>
      <description>Step 1: Watch Tech Monopolies: Last Week Tonight with John Oliver (HBO)
Step 2: Use EFF&amp;rsquo;s Action Center to contact your representatives about the Open App Markets Act
Step 3: Use democracy.io to write to your reps about the &amp;ldquo;American Choice and Innovation Online Act&amp;rdquo;. For example:
Subject: American Choice and Innovation Online Act
As your constituent, I urge you to support the American Choice and Innovation Online Act (S.2992). The legislation aims to prevent Big Tech companies from &amp;ldquo;self-preferencing&amp;rdquo; their own products at the expense of competitors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell My WiFi Love Her</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-06-04-tell-my-wifi-love-her/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 18:01:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-06-04-tell-my-wifi-love-her/</guid>
      <description>We have a lovely area on the lower slope of our backyard with nice outdoor furniture and a huge umbrella, but it has weak wifi signal. The only wireless access point in the house is a single, ancient router in the living room. I would love to work from this lower slope; it&amp;rsquo;s so peaceful and quiet. So, I bought a second wifi router, installed OpenWRT on it, and spent most of the day trying to configure an 802.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022-05-29</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-05-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 20:50:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-05-29/</guid>
      <description>Today was a good day. I spent a lot of time working on this new Hugo-powered site and I&amp;rsquo;ve officially relaunched evanstucker.com! I&amp;rsquo;m still learning how to make Hugo do what I want, and I still need to add some features like some kind of decentralized commenting system&amp;hellip;
Regarding Andrea, she&amp;rsquo;s still recovering really quickly! We got decent sleep last night, and she was able to go most of the day with no painkillers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Mobile Phone Plan</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-05-29-new-mobile-phone-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 12:50:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-05-29-new-mobile-phone-plan/</guid>
      <description>I got a new Pinephone Pro earlier this year, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to find an inexpensive mobile phone plan with minimal data . I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to add this phone to my existing Google Fi account, because I&amp;rsquo;m trying to de-Google myself, and it seems counterproductive to give Google more money if my goal is to stop being their customer. In my research, I found a fantastic Reddit community named &amp;ldquo;NoContract&amp;rdquo; whose goal is to &amp;ldquo;Reclaim your freedom &amp;ndash; and your wallet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wrecking Recommendation Engines</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-02-28-wrecking-recommendation-engines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:32:26 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-02-28-wrecking-recommendation-engines/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always had eclectic taste, but I&amp;rsquo;m really enjoying wrecking Netflix&amp;rsquo;s (and other streaming services) recommendation engine lately. It appears to have no idea what I am anymore. I typically watch weird indie movies and random shows from 2 to 10 years ago on my account, but I also watch a bunch of stuff with the kids - we just finished Kipo and the Age of Wonderbeasts (it was decent). And I occationally watch blockbuster movies with Andrea, or family movies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SuperbOwl MMXXII</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-02-13-superbowl-mmxxii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:49:09 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-02-13-superbowl-mmxxii/</guid>
      <description>On this very special Superb Owl Sunday, a very generous owl gave us this OWL PELLET! Amazing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022-02-12</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-02-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:41:19 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-02-12/</guid>
      <description>I finally worked out the MIME type bug I was having with IPFS. I think I&amp;rsquo;ll relaunch my website soon!
Rhys got a pretty nice haircut today.
He and Andrea went to baseball practice, and Corbin and I went on a long bike ride: Cadman park, then down the hill, past the karate dojo, all the way to Costco. We got a berry smoothie and ice cream, then walked back up the hill, and went home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>login.xyz</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-02-08-login-xyz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 11:26:31 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-02-08-login-xyz/</guid>
      <description>I just skimmed https://blog.mycrypto.com/sign-in-with-ethereum-an-alternative-to-centralized-identity-providers. This reminds me partially of what uPort and 3Box are doing. I&amp;rsquo;m still very interested in a passwordless future where we use our wallets to sign in to things. Looks like this article is about https://login.xyz/, which has an OIDC server here: https://docs.login.xyz/servers/oidc-server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikita Ostapenco</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-01-22-nikita-ostapenco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 10:04:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-01-22-nikita-ostapenco/</guid>
      <description>I discovered a Moldovan artist named Nikita Ostapenco while shopping for a secret Santa gift for a co-worker. Check out their art! Lots of amazing colors, and interesting characters and backgrounds!
https://www.artfinder.com/artist/ostapenconikita/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-06-28</title>
      <link>/posts/2021-06-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 21:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2021-06-28/</guid>
      <description>I bought Corbin the Kurzgesagt gratitude journal for his birthday and I wanted to practice doing it with him. Here&amp;rsquo;s my entry for today:
Q: What happened today?
I had a hanger-induced lunchistetial crisis.
I went to Woody&amp;rsquo;s at Pacific Beach
I started reading the US Sailing Basic Cruising book
Q: Did something good happen to you?
I had a peaceful lunch at Woody&amp;rsquo;s - beautiful weather, great view right on the beach, cool weird surf music, stoic servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Response to Technobabble, Libertarian Derp and Bitcoin</title>
      <link>/posts/2021-05-21-a-response-to-technobabble-libertarian-derp-and-bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 19:59:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2021-05-21-a-response-to-technobabble-libertarian-derp-and-bitcoin/</guid>
      <description>I wrote this in bare HTML. It&amp;rsquo;s available here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Evans Tucker, and this is my personal website. I like to write things and share them. On October 11th, 1999 I launched my original website - it was a PHP content management system (CMS) that had themes and a comment system that I wrote myself - I was really proud of it! Then I tried to migrate it to Blogspot, but I gave up. After that I spent a lot of time on Friendster (now defunct), MySpace, Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art</title>
      <link>/lists/art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lists/art/</guid>
      <description>Artists
Christine Hausserman uses specialty coated glass beads and pieces to create stunning mosaics. Courtney Scruggs creates gorgeous, terrifying bronze scultures with a strong nautical style. Elisabeth Hale makes amazing, beautifully textured paintings of inspiring landscapes like the Grand Canyon, Arches National Park, and various coastal scenes. Grant Pecoff has mastered the art of painting water and beautiful beach scenes from all over the world. He has a very clean, minimalistic style that&amp;rsquo;s really appealing to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Newsletters</title>
      <link>/lists/blockchain-newsletters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lists/blockchain-newsletters/</guid>
      <description> https://weekinethereumnews.com/ https://thedefiant.substack.com/ https://ethhub.substack.com/ https://messari.io/ https://ournetwork.substack.com/ mulitple chains https://decrypt.co/ https://forms.technologyreview.com/chain-letter/ </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evans&#39;s Wishlist</title>
      <link>/lists/evanss-wishlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lists/evanss-wishlist/</guid>
      <description>Locksport things
Genesis Lockpick Set $25 and/or Covert Companion $90 Optional Comb picks $15 - not necessary if I get the Covert Companion. Optional CI Practice Lock $50, but I also have plenty of locks to mess with at home too. Musical Instruments
Teenage Engineering Pocket Operator PO-35 Speak $100 - this thing is super cool, but complicated, but I really want to learn how to do synth and patterns and stuff!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-fungible Tokens (NFTs)</title>
      <link>/lists/nfts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lists/nfts/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not an NFT collector, but every once in a while I find a collection that&amp;rsquo;s interesting. Here are my favorites so far:
2017-06 CryptoPunks - I think these might be the first NFTs? I&amp;rsquo;m still baffled that people pay so much for pixelated pictures of punks. 2017-11 CryptoKitties - Maybe the first NFT game? Not much of a game, but it was an interesting experiment in how to gamify NFTs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
