<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>tech on Evans Tucker</title>
    <link>/categories/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tech on Evans Tucker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>[CC0](http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/) Evans Tucker has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 18:01:12 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tell My WiFi Love Her</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-06-04-tell-my-wifi-love-her/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 18:01:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-06-04-tell-my-wifi-love-her/</guid>
      <description>We have a lovely area on the lower slope of our backyard with nice outdoor furniture and a huge umbrella, but it has weak wifi signal. The only wireless access point in the house is a single, ancient router in the living room. I would love to work from this lower slope; it&amp;rsquo;s so peaceful and quiet. So, I bought a second wifi router, installed OpenWRT on it, and spent most of the day trying to configure an 802.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Mobile Phone Plan</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-05-29-new-mobile-phone-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 12:50:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-05-29-new-mobile-phone-plan/</guid>
      <description>I got a new Pinephone Pro earlier this year, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to find an inexpensive mobile phone plan with minimal data . I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to add this phone to my existing Google Fi account, because I&amp;rsquo;m trying to de-Google myself, and it seems counterproductive to give Google more money if my goal is to stop being their customer. In my research, I found a fantastic Reddit community named &amp;ldquo;NoContract&amp;rdquo; whose goal is to &amp;ldquo;Reclaim your freedom &amp;ndash; and your wallet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wrecking Recommendation Engines</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-02-28-wrecking-recommendation-engines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:32:26 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-02-28-wrecking-recommendation-engines/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always had eclectic taste, but I&amp;rsquo;m really enjoying wrecking Netflix&amp;rsquo;s (and other streaming services) recommendation engine lately. It appears to have no idea what I am anymore. I typically watch weird indie movies and random shows from 2 to 10 years ago on my account, but I also watch a bunch of stuff with the kids - we just finished Kipo and the Age of Wonderbeasts (it was decent). And I occationally watch blockbuster movies with Andrea, or family movies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>login.xyz</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-02-08-login-xyz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 11:26:31 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-02-08-login-xyz/</guid>
      <description>I just skimmed https://blog.mycrypto.com/sign-in-with-ethereum-an-alternative-to-centralized-identity-providers. This reminds me partially of what uPort and 3Box are doing. I&amp;rsquo;m still very interested in a passwordless future where we use our wallets to sign in to things. Looks like this article is about https://login.xyz/, which has an OIDC server here: https://docs.login.xyz/servers/oidc-server.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
