<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lists on Evans Tucker</title>
    <link>/lists/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lists on Evans Tucker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>[CC0](http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/) Evans Tucker has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights.</copyright><atom:link href="/lists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Art</title>
      <link>/lists/art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lists/art/</guid>
      <description>Artists
Christine Hausserman uses specialty coated glass beads and pieces to create stunning mosaics. Courtney Scruggs creates gorgeous, terrifying bronze scultures with a strong nautical style. Elisabeth Hale makes amazing, beautifully textured paintings of inspiring landscapes like the Grand Canyon, Arches National Park, and various coastal scenes. Grant Pecoff has mastered the art of painting water and beautiful beach scenes from all over the world. He has a very clean, minimalistic style that&amp;rsquo;s really appealing to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Newsletters</title>
      <link>/lists/blockchain-newsletters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lists/blockchain-newsletters/</guid>
      <description> https://weekinethereumnews.com/ https://thedefiant.substack.com/ https://ethhub.substack.com/ https://messari.io/ https://ournetwork.substack.com/ mulitple chains https://decrypt.co/ https://forms.technologyreview.com/chain-letter/ </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evans&#39;s Wishlist</title>
      <link>/lists/evanss-wishlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lists/evanss-wishlist/</guid>
      <description>Locksport things
Genesis Lockpick Set $25 and/or Covert Companion $90 Optional Comb picks $15 - not necessary if I get the Covert Companion. Optional CI Practice Lock $50, but I also have plenty of locks to mess with at home too. Musical Instruments
Teenage Engineering Pocket Operator PO-35 Speak $100 - this thing is super cool, but complicated, but I really want to learn how to do synth and patterns and stuff!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-fungible Tokens (NFTs)</title>
      <link>/lists/nfts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lists/nfts/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not an NFT collector, but every once in a while I find a collection that&amp;rsquo;s interesting. Here are my favorites so far:
2017-06 CryptoPunks - I think these might be the first NFTs? I&amp;rsquo;m still baffled that people pay so much for pixelated pictures of punks. 2017-11 CryptoKitties - Maybe the first NFT game? Not much of a game, but it was an interesting experiment in how to gamify NFTs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
